OSMAR GRAÇA



CONTACT INFORMATION

- osmar.graca@icloud.com
- Sacavém, Lisbon, Portugal
- +351 963 125 443
- Dec 16, 1997
- Portuguese
- https://pt.linkedin.com/in/osmar-gra% C3%A7a-6b44b4143

SKILLS

- Java
- Python
- HTML
- SQL

LANGUAGES

- Portuguese | Native
- English | Advanced
- Spanish | Intermediate

OBJECTIVE

I am highly ambitious and curious, with experience in sales and management. I am meticulous, dedicated and responsible. I intend to change my career path and enter the IT world, in a company where I can learn and grow continuously.

EXPERIENCE

SHOP MANAGER

Valor do Tempo. Lisbon, Portugal | 2019 - 2023

- In 2020, I became the Manager due to exceeding daily sales targets with a consultative and value-focused approach regarding customer support.
- Supervising a team of 6-9 people;
- · Supporting customers with complaints against the shop and products;
- · Solving daily shop and inter-team problems;
- · Responsible for on-the-job training of new team members;
- Responsible for making schedules;
- · Product returns and exchanges;
- Opening and closing of the shop;
- Controlling cash registers at various counters to ensure adequate cash provisions;
- Effective interaction with stakeholders for ordering, stock control etc.

NATIONAL FLEET MANAGER

DB Schenker. Loures, Lisbon | Jul 2016 - Jul 2019

- Control of Opening and closing incoming and outgoing trucks;
- Management of the national truck fleet;
- Creation of maps concerning the route of Volkswagen trucks;
- Creation of AUTO EUROPA maps;
- Telephone customer service;
- Filing;
- Scanning;
- Consistently met my short and long-term targets.

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEERING

Autonomous University of Lisbon. Lisbon, Portugal | 2021 - Present

The main technologies that I've been using are Java, Python, C, HTML, SQL.

MANAGEMENT SUPPORT TECHNICIAN

DUAL – German- Portuguese Chamber of Commerce and Industry . Moscavide, Lisbon | 2015 - 2018

GSCE (GENERAL CERTIFICATION)

All saints Catholic School. United Kingdom | 2010 - 2014